Hey BrazilJS Folks!
BrazilJS pueblo!
Hi, my name is Sérgio Lopes
Hola, mi nombre es Sergio Lopes
I am an instructor and developer at Alura and Caelum
Soy instructor y desarrollador en Alura y Caelum
where I work mainly with Front End
Donde trabajo principalmente con esta parte del Front
mobile, optimization, performance
de mobile, optimizaciones, rendimiento
and things like that
y similares
I want to invite you to BrazilJS, this year!
Y quería invitarle a participar Este año, la BrazilJS
The main JavaScript conference in the Universe!
La conferencia principal Universo JavaScript
Which is happening in August, in Porto Alegre
Que va a pasar ahora en agosto, en Porto Alegre
and I will be there!
Voy a estar allá, pero sobre todo
But there will also be a lot of interesting people in this event!
porque tendrá mucha gente interesante este evento!
A lot of amazing things! I was looking at the website now
Yo estaba buscando ahora en el site
and the amount of impressive talks that will happen there
y la cantidad de conferencias que va a estar allá
will be amazing!
será verdaderamente increíble!
So, don't waste this chance!
De manera no lo pierda!
The main JavaScript conference in the world
Principal conferencia JavaScript del mundo
In Porto Alegre, in August
Que pasará ahora agosto
and we will meet there! See you!
y nos encontramos allá Gracias!